Mike Garringer

Web Developer

Location: Austin, TX, 78751 | **Phone**: 913-549-8271 | **Email**: <u>michaelleelyngarringer@gmail.com</u> **LinkedIn**:https://www.linkedin.com/in/mike-garringer-029551131/ | **Github**: github.com/MichaelGarringer |

Portfolio: portfoliomikeq.herokuapp.com/

Web Developer with a background in Political Science. Experienced in Javascript, HTML, and CSS with formal training at the University of Texas. Offers a creative approach to problem solving and perseverance when dealing with adversity. Holds over five years of experience in customer service, with an emphasis on face-to-face customer relations and a history of managing others. A detail-oriented, people person who is willing to go the extra mile to ensure the customer is fully satisfied.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development University of Texas, Austin, TX 2019

Bachelor's in Political Science Major, Anthropology Minor University of Kansas, Lawrence, KS 2012-2016

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, Javascript, CSS

Applications: JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, & ReactJS

PROJECTS

League Manager (WIP)

github.com/rise-shine/FFBLeagueManager | ffbleaguemanager.herokuapp.com/

A simple app that will ultimately allow a user to manage Fantasy Football teams and leagues. Currently displays roster, football news and user info.

- Created user login and styled page
- Technologies used: ReactJS, Javascript, Axios, CSS

Gift Scribe

https://github.com/rise-shine/Project-2 | https://giftscribe.herokuapp.com/

A simple app for creating lists of ideas of gifts for friends or family. User logs in and from there can create lists of friends and a list of ideas for each friend.

- Adding and deleting friends to the friends list, React routing
- Technologies Used: ReactJS, Javascript, CSS, MongoDB

WORK EXPERIENCE

Airport Manager/ Lead Customer Service Representative

SuperShuttle and Execucar of Austin and San Antonio - Austin, TX

March 2017 to August 2019

Managed all aspects of on-site operations for an airport shuttle company

- Managed 5-7 full-time employees, including training, hiring and termination
- Ensured the accuracy of payroll and cash handling

ADDITIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

Cashier/Customer Service Dillons Supermarkets, Inc. - Lawrence, KS

May 2015 to December 2016